<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Riding Bytes</title>
    <link>http://ridingbytes.com/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Riding Bytes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2015, RIDING BYTES; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://ridingbytes.com/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Development</title>
      <link>http://ridingbytes.com/services/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ridingbytes.com/services/development/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;development:c51f1b783d6e6b3bc97ce5906e9605d3&#34;&gt;Development&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RIDING BYTES offers a variety of custom development services. Starting from small
scripts for task automation or data manipulation, up to enterprise server based
solutions, like content management systems or enterprise resource planning
systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next sections provide a small overview of used systems, technologies
and the provided services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;python:c51f1b783d6e6b3bc97ce5906e9605d3&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://python.org&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; is a modern, powerful and fast programming
language, that runs on all platforms. It is successfully used in thousands of
real-world business applications around the world, including many large and
mission critical system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer custom tailored programs built with &lt;a href=&#34;http://python.org&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt;, starting
from a small command line script up to full web systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;plone:c51f1b783d6e6b3bc97ce5906e9605d3&#34;&gt;Plone&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://plone.org&#34;&gt;Plone&lt;/a&gt; is one of the biggest and most popular content
management solutions which uses &lt;a href=&#34;http://python.org&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; under the hood. It
has been actively developed since 2001, is available in more than 40 languages,
and has the best security track record of any major CMS. It is owned by the
Plone Foundation, a 501&amp;copy;(3) not-for-profit organization, and is available for
all major operating systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer full service and customization for &lt;a href=&#34;http://plone.org&#34;&gt;Plone&lt;/a&gt;,
integrate it in your new or existing infrastructure and support you with the
necessary consultancy and trainings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;odoo:c51f1b783d6e6b3bc97ce5906e9605d3&#34;&gt;Odoo&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.odoo.com&#34;&gt;Odoo&lt;/a&gt; is another open source enterprise resource planning
(ERP) and customer relations management (CRM) system, which is built with
&lt;a href=&#34;http://python.org&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt;. The main applications included in
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.odoo.com&#34;&gt;Odoo&lt;/a&gt; are an Open Source CRM, Website Builder, eCommerce,
Project Management, Billing &amp;amp; Accounting, Point of Sale, Human Resources,
Marketing, Manufacturing, Purchase Management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer full service and customization for &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.odoo.com&#34;&gt;Odoo&lt;/a&gt;,
integrate it in your new or existing infrastructure and support you with the
necessary consultancy and trainings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;flask:c51f1b783d6e6b3bc97ce5906e9605d3&#34;&gt;Flask&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You want to build your custom server solution from scratch? Than
&lt;a href=&#34;http://flask.pocoo.org&#34;&gt;Flask&lt;/a&gt; is the right solution.
&lt;a href=&#34;http://flask.pocoo.org&#34;&gt;Flask&lt;/a&gt; is a microframework for
&lt;a href=&#34;http://python.org&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; based on Werkzeug, Jinja 2 and good intentions.  It
can basically handle any database backend and ships with powerful extensions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer complete support in the planning of the architecture and the development of
any &lt;a href=&#34;http://flask.pocoo.org&#34;&gt;Flask&lt;/a&gt; based solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;extjs:c51f1b783d6e6b3bc97ce5906e9605d3&#34;&gt;ExtJS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Desktop application? Mobile/Phone application? Both?
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sencha.com/products/extjs&#34;&gt;ExtJS&lt;/a&gt; provides a solution for all
devices. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sencha.com/products/extjs&#34;&gt;ExtJS&lt;/a&gt; is a sophisticated
JavaScript framework with the capability to build enterprise applications, which
handles thousands of data records with great performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We provide the full service, starting from the planning phase up to development
and hosting. Powered by &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/atom/electron&#34;&gt;Electron&lt;/a&gt;, it is even
possible to run dedicated applications on MacOS, Linux and Windows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;hugo:c51f1b783d6e6b3bc97ce5906e9605d3&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You want to have a static website? Something that does not depend on
administrative privileges, databases, runtimes, interpreters or external
libraries? Than probably &lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; is the right thing for you.
Sites built with &lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; can be deployed on S3, GitHub Pages,
Dropbox or any web host.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer a full integration and customization from any web based template for
&lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;. Either you offer a template, choose a nice one
from &lt;a href=&#34;https://wrapbootstrap.com/themes&#34;&gt;{wrap}bootstrap&lt;/a&gt;, or we assemble one for
you based on a mock up.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UIUX</title>
      <link>http://ridingbytes.com/services/uiux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ridingbytes.com/services/uiux/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;ui-ux:bf92aecb4a13be047ab9446fb93b6fd0&#34;&gt;UI/UX&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These two terms stand for &lt;em&gt;User Interface&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;User Experience&lt;/em&gt;. While the
first one is mainly concerned with the layout of application elements, the
latter one cares about how the interaction with the application feels to the user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both terms are linked to each other and highly influence the user acceptance of
the finished application/product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RIDING BYTES is specialized in web based user interfaces, which provide a great
user experience by logical application flows and an intuitive layout.  We offer
consulting, support and development of custom web-, mobile-, or desktop
applications.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting</title>
      <link>http://ridingbytes.com/services/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ridingbytes.com/services/consulting/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;consulting:a25d6bd4dcb7d62219c6846057abf7cb&#34;&gt;Consulting&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Communication is the key for a successful partnership in business relations and
horseback riding. We offer consulting services, to understand the needs and the
requirement of our customers and to provide the professional expertise of all
our knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer in house consulting services to analyze current workflows, optimize
business processes and find the right IT solutions to support the management or
the staff to get their work done more effective and efficient.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administration</title>
      <link>http://ridingbytes.com/services/administration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ridingbytes.com/services/administration/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;administration:13211676e978b46d236d2a86bdb3cd25&#34;&gt;Administration&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every computer system need an optimal environment to work properly. It is
necessary to monitor, update and run several maintenance tasks on business
critical servers periodically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We provide support for the deployment and maintenance of our software solutions
or offer the complete service in house or remote through a secure tunnel
connection. We support servers based on Linux, MacOS or Windows and help you
with all administrative questions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>