<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mba on RIDING BYTES</title>
    <link>/categories/mba/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mba on RIDING BYTES</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2015-2018, RIDING BYTES; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/mba/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Master of Business Administration (MBA)</title>
      <link>/2017/06/27/riding-bytes-mba/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/27/riding-bytes-mba/</guid>
      <description>Herzlichen Glückwunsch zum erfolgreichen Abschluss Das einzigartige Programm zur Entwicklung von Führungspersönlichkeiten der Hochschule Kempten, fand dieses Jahr Ihren Höhepunkt, mit der Übergabe der Urkunden an die MBA Absolventen, im Rahmen einer feierlichen Zeremonie, im Stadttheater Kempten.
Die Festveranstaltung, die ab 18:00 Uhr im Theatersaal stattfand, stand den Absolventinnen und Absolventen, ihren Begleitpersonen sowie auch den Professorinnen und Professoren der Kemptener Denkfabrik offen.
Die Mitarbeiter, Freunde und Partner der Riding Bytes, gratulieren der Geschäftsleitung, Herrn Ramon Bartl, herzlichst zum erfolgreichen Abschluss des MBA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MBA Master Thesis: Impact of Netiquette on Email Communication</title>
      <link>/2017/01/29/mba-master-thesis-impact-of-netiquette-on-email-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 10:08:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/29/mba-master-thesis-impact-of-netiquette-on-email-communication/</guid>
      <description>Impact of Netiquette on Email Communication Emails are likely to get evaluated more negative than maybe intended of the sender. Therefore, we should consider carefully what and how we write Emails, because every human has a need for self-esteem, respect and courtesy when communicating with others.
I investigated in my Master Thesis the impact of Netiquette on Email communication and found out, that writing in a respectful and courteous way has significant positive effects on the recipient.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>