<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on RIDING BYTES</title>
    <link>/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on RIDING BYTES</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2015-2018, RIDING BYTES; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Development</title>
      <link>/services/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/development/</guid>
      <description>Development RIDING BYTES offers a variety of custom development services. Starting from small scripts for task automation or data manipulation, up to enterprise server based solutions, like content management systems or enterprise resource planning systems.
The next sections provide a small overview of used systems, technologies and the provided services.
  SENAITE is a universal ISO 17025 compliant LIMS for chemistry and micro biology - used in anything from agriculture, food and beverages, water quality management, mining etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UIUX</title>
      <link>/services/uiux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/uiux/</guid>
      <description>UI/UX These two terms stand for User Interface and User Experience. While the first one is mainly concerned with the layout of application elements, the latter one cares about how the interaction with the application feels to the user.
Both terms are linked to each other and highly influence the user acceptance of the finished application/product.
Case Study: Bika Spotlight Search Bika Spotlight Search offers an MAC OS X like Search UI for Bika LIMS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting</title>
      <link>/services/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/consulting/</guid>
      <description>Consulting A consultant (from Latin: consultare &amp;ldquo;to discuss&amp;rdquo;) is a professional who provides professional or expert advice (Source: Wikipedia).
It is one of the most important services to ensure the planned and proposed IT solution meets the needs of the customer.
What we offer We offer all our professional expertise and knowledge in house or remote to analyze current workflows, optimize business processes and find the right IT solutions to support the management or the staff to get their work done more effective and efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administration</title>
      <link>/services/administration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/administration/</guid>
      <description>Administration The right IT solution needs the right operating environment to work properly. Server based IT are always coupled with administrative tasks such as Installation, Configuration, Updates, Monitoring, Optimizations, Backups, Custom Scripts, Domain-, Hosting-, DNS- and Email Setup, Operational Support, &amp;hellip;
What we offer We provide support for the installation, deployment and maintenance of our software solutions or offer the complete service in house or remote through a secure tunnel connection.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>