<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on RIDING BYTES</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on RIDING BYTES</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2015-2018, RIDING BYTES; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 21:15:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SENAITE, Professional Open Source LIMS</title>
      <link>/2018/01/06/senaite-professional-open-source-lims/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 21:15:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/06/senaite-professional-open-source-lims/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
 &amp;nbsp;
3 months ago, Riding Bytes and Naralabs decided to join efforts in bringing Open Source Laboratory Information Management Systems (LIMS) to the next level. Now, after 3 months of hard work, Riding Bytes and Naralabs are proud to finally announce the first official release of SENAITE. This announcement comes at the beginning of a new year, and we also want this release to be the beginning of a new era for Open Source LIMS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLONE Conference 2017 – Digital Experience Conference</title>
      <link>/2017/10/16/riding-bytes-plone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/16/riding-bytes-plone/</guid>
      <description>Von den neusten schöpferischen Gedankengängen - über die Umsetzung - bis zum Fortschritt Auch dieses Jahr wieder ist die RIDING BYTES auf der PLONE Konferenz, die 2017 in Barcelona Ihre Pforten öffnet, vertreten.
Mit einem Vortrag über die JSON API Schnittstelle, erhalten Sie unter anderem Einsicht über die neuartige Weiterentwicklung um moderne JavaScript Applikationen an das Plone CMS anzubinden.
Using a Plone JSON API to interface modern Web Applications https://2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master of Business Administration (MBA)</title>
      <link>/2017/06/27/riding-bytes-mba/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/27/riding-bytes-mba/</guid>
      <description>Herzlichen Glückwunsch zum erfolgreichen Abschluss Das einzigartige Programm zur Entwicklung von Führungspersönlichkeiten der Hochschule Kempten, fand dieses Jahr Ihren Höhepunkt, mit der Übergabe der Urkunden an die MBA Absolventen, im Rahmen einer feierlichen Zeremonie, im Stadttheater Kempten.
Die Festveranstaltung, die ab 18:00 Uhr im Theatersaal stattfand, stand den Absolventinnen und Absolventen, ihren Begleitpersonen sowie auch den Professorinnen und Professoren der Kemptener Denkfabrik offen.
Die Mitarbeiter, Freunde und Partner der Riding Bytes, gratulieren der Geschäftsleitung, Herrn Ramon Bartl, herzlichst zum erfolgreichen Abschluss des MBA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coding Know-how kehrt in die Metropolregion Nürnberg ein</title>
      <link>/2017/06/20/riding-bytes-in-der-metropolregion-nuernberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 17:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/20/riding-bytes-in-der-metropolregion-nuernberg/</guid>
      <description>Neu in der Stadt Offenheit in den Köpfen und Nachhaltigkeit in der Umsetzung kennzeichnen unsere Projekte.
Im Mai 2017 verlegt die Riding Bytes seinen Firmensitz nach Fürth.
Moderne Komplettlösungen im Laborbereich werden nun von der Kleeblattstadt aus, für nationale und internationale Kunden ausgebaut.
Ein individuelles Funktionsspektrum, basierend auf Open Source Lösungen spricht die Sprache der Zukunft.
Das Bika Open Source LIMS Projekt ist als Marktführer im Laborbereich, das Fundament, das den komplexen Besonderheiten des jeweiligen Labors angepasst werden kann.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to configure OpenLDAP to be usable for OwnCloud</title>
      <link>/2017/03/06/how-to-configure-openldap-to-be-usable-for-owncloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 11:24:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/06/how-to-configure-openldap-to-be-usable-for-owncloud/</guid>
      <description>OwnCloud and OpenLDAP We recently integrated OwnCloud 9 in our IT infrastructure and wanted to hook it up with our OpenLDAP server, which is running on a Ubuntu 16.04 LTS Xenial Xerus Server.
After installing the required LDAP user and group App in OwnCloud, we could hook our LDAP server into OwnCloud. However, the Group selection to narrow down the users who are allowed to log into OwnCloud was disabled, since the memberOf LDAP Overlay was not yet supported by our companys LDAP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MBA Master Thesis: Impact of Netiquette on Email Communication</title>
      <link>/2017/01/29/mba-master-thesis-impact-of-netiquette-on-email-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 10:08:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/29/mba-master-thesis-impact-of-netiquette-on-email-communication/</guid>
      <description>Impact of Netiquette on Email Communication Emails are likely to get evaluated more negative than maybe intended of the sender. Therefore, we should consider carefully what and how we write Emails, because every human has a need for self-esteem, respect and courtesy when communicating with others.
I investigated in my Master Thesis the impact of Netiquette on Email communication and found out, that writing in a respectful and courteous way has significant positive effects on the recipient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Odoo: Developer mode</title>
      <link>/2016/03/06/odoo-developer-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 23:44:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/06/odoo-developer-mode/</guid>
      <description>Odoo: Access Technical Features In Odoo 9 you might miss the Technical Features checkbox in the Access Rights of your user. These settings are now visible if you activate the Developer Mode from the About menu.
I had to access this many times during development and found out, that I lose too much time accessing the menu and clicking on the button. I had to change this!
I created this small Bookmarklet, which toggles the developer mode by a single click&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Odoo: Dynamic image resizing</title>
      <link>/2016/01/04/odoo-dynamic-image-resizing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 11:44:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/01/04/odoo-dynamic-image-resizing/</guid>
      <description>Odoo: Scale images on the fly Odoo uses Python Imaging Library (PIL) to support image resizing on the fly. This functionality ships with the image.py module, which is located in openerp.tools.image.
Problem I implemented a custom model which defined a binary field called image:
class MyModel(models.Model): _name = &amp;#39;my.model&amp;#39; image = fields.Binary(&amp;#39;Image&amp;#39;, required=True) image_filename = fields.Char(&amp;#34;Image Filename&amp;#34;) I wanted to use this model within in a website view, but struggled with finding a suitable image source URL for the image field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Odoo: Remember the filename of binary files</title>
      <link>/2016/01/02/odoo-remember-the-filename-of-binary-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2016 19:26:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/01/02/odoo-remember-the-filename-of-binary-files/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;odoo-remember-the-filename-of-binary-files&#34;&gt;Odoo: Remember the filename of binary files&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;problem&#34;&gt;Problem&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to use a binary field to store image data to a custom model.
Therefore I used a field of the type &lt;code&gt;Binary&lt;/code&gt; in my model. Unfortunately only
the base64 encoded file was stored in the database but not the filename. This
resulted in an unknown binary file download with the name of the current model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIDING BYTES-Bika Labs-Partnership</title>
      <link>/2015/12/17/riding-bytes-bika-labs-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 21:53:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/17/riding-bytes-bika-labs-partnership/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;riding-bytes-bika-labs-partnership&#34;&gt;RIDING BYTES / Bika Labs - Partnership&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;!-- &lt;blockquote class=&#34;twitter-tweet&#34;&gt;&lt;p lang=&#34;en&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;More than just a Company – A strong Network of Partners.&lt;br&gt;RIDING BYTES is now official Partner of Bika Lab Systems &lt;a href=&#34;https://t.co/07B6ap3DMO&#34;&gt;https://t.co/07B6ap3DMO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; RIDING BYTES (@ridingbytes) &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/ridingbytes/status/677201899674800129?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;December 16, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src=&#34;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
 --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since December 15, 2015 RIDING BYTES and Bika Labs (South Africa) are official Partners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plone Commander</title>
      <link>/2015/09/23/plone-commander/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 20:26:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/09/23/plone-commander/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;plone-commander&#34;&gt;Plone Commander&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ridingbytes/plone.commander/releases&#34;&gt;Plone Commander&lt;/a&gt; is a
cross platform application built with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sencha.com/products/extjs&#34;&gt;ExtJS&lt;/a&gt;
and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/atom/electron&#34;&gt;Electron&lt;/a&gt;. It allows you to find, view,
edit and explore Plone contents with ease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is free, open source and &lt;a href=&#34;https://opensource.org/licenses/MIT&#34;&gt;MIT&lt;/a&gt; licensed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--
&lt;figure class=&#34;e-block-skin image-left&#34;&gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;/img/blog/plone-commander.jpg&#34; width=&#34;85%&#34; /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;
--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>