<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on RIDING BYTES</title>
    <link>/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on RIDING BYTES</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2015-2018, RIDING BYTES; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bika Spotlight Search</title>
      <link>/portfolio/bika-spotlight-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/bika-spotlight-search/</guid>
      <description> Overview Bika Spotlight Search is a modern JavaScript application written with CoffeeScript and based on the BackboneJS framework. It communicates with Bika LIMS through plone.jsonapi.routes.
See it in Action   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bika Commander</title>
      <link>/portfolio/bika-commander/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/bika-commander/</guid>
      <description> Overview Bika Commander is a cross platform web application based on Electron and ExtJS. It communicates with Bika LIMS through plone.jsonapi.routes.
See it in Action   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpenleder ERP</title>
      <link>/portfolio/alpenleder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/alpenleder/</guid>
      <description>Overview Alpenleder is an international bag manufacturing company and retailer. They have special requirements to their IT system, like shop functionality, reseller and customer login, multi-language support, product variants, inventory and HR capabilities. Odoo 9 serves all their needs and is ready for future requirements by customizations from RIDING BYTES.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIDING BYTES ERP</title>
      <link>/portfolio/ridingbytes-odoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/ridingbytes-odoo/</guid>
      <description>Overview RIDING BYTES manages a variety of business intelligence tasks with Odoo 9. Custom Report-, Quotation-, Sale Order-, and Invoice Templates streamline the whole order process for national and international customers. Project and Timesheet Bookings gives customers transparence to their projects and allows controlling and planning at any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIDING BYTES Website</title>
      <link>/portfolio/ridingbytes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/ridingbytes/</guid>
      <description>Overview The RIDING BYTES website is based on a general-purpose website framework called Hugo. Unlike systems like WordPress, Ghost and Drupal, Hugo doesn’t depend on administrative privileges, databases, runtimes, interpreters or external libraries. It creates the website only once, when you create new content.
About Sites built with Hugo are extremely fast and very secure. Hugo sites can be hosted anywhere, including Heroku, GoDaddy, DreamHost, GitHub Pages, Google Cloud Storage, Amazon S3 and CloudFront, and work well with CDNs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plone JSON API</title>
      <link>/portfolio/plone-jsonapi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/plone-jsonapi/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is an add-on package for plone.jsonapi.core which provides resource URLs for Plone standard contents (and more).
Motivation The routes package is built on top of the plone.jsonapi.core package to allow Plone developers to build modern (JavaScript) web UIs which communicate through a RESTful API with their Plone site.
Compatibility The plone.jsonapi.routes is compatible with Plone 4.
Documentation Read the latest documentation: http://plonejsonapiroutes.readthedocs.org
Where to get? Get the latest version on the Python Package Index: https://pypi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plone Commander</title>
      <link>/portfolio/plone-commander/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/plone-commander/</guid>
      <description> Overview Plone Commander is a cross platform web application based on Electron and ExtJS. It communicates with Plone through plone.jsonapi.routes.
See it in Action   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>