<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Email on RIDING BYTES</title>
    <link>http://ridingbytes.com/categories/email/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Email on RIDING BYTES</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://ridingbytes.com/categories/email/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>MBA Master Thesis: Impact of Netiquette on Email Communication</title>
      <link>http://ridingbytes.com/2017/01/29/mba-master-thesis-impact-of-netiquette-on-email-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 10:08:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ridingbytes.com/2017/01/29/mba-master-thesis-impact-of-netiquette-on-email-communication/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;impact-of-netiquette-on-email-communication&#34;&gt;Impact of Netiquette on Email Communication&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emails are likely to get evaluated more negative than maybe intended of the sender.
Therefore, we should consider carefully what and how we write Emails, because every
human has a need for self-esteem, respect and courtesy when communicating with
others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I investigated in my Master Thesis the impact of Netiquette on Email
communication and found out, that writing in a respectful and courteous way has
significant positive effects on the recipient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today’s organizations depend heavily on the use of email. Information is
exchanged to reduce uncertainty and resolve equivocality to accomplish internal
tasks or coordinate activities. Often issues are ill-defined in the brevity of
emails and thus, the problem is a lack of clarity, not data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, due to its text-based nature, email has also reduced availabilities to
convey nonverbal cues, which might support understanding. This makes it
especially difficult to convey emotion or ambiguity, such as irony or sarcasm
over email. Nevertheless, senders’ intentionally and unintentionally communicate
emotion over email and emotions are likely to be the reason for
miscommunication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aim of this study was to investigate the impact of Netiquette on the
recipients’ level of understanding, job satisfaction, amount of uncertainty and
perception of senders’ likability. An electronic questionnaire was developed,
where participants (N=105) had to evaluate four email samples, which were
ostensibly written by a superior or subordinate. All emails contained a negative
message (rejection, criticism), but were either delivered just by their content
or included common Netiquette rules. Results have shown, that the email samples
with Netiquette significantly improved the understanding and job satisfaction,
reduced uncertainty and let the sender appear more favorable. Additionally, the
organizational status of the sender resulted in a leveraging positive effect on
job satisfaction and evidence for gender differences were found in the results.
Implications for managers and organizations are discussed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;downloads&#34;&gt;Downloads&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please feel free to download the MBA Master Thesis and Netiquette Guide to build
up your own or your organizations&amp;rsquo; Email Policy, because communication matters –
everywhere. Thanks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;rb-download dl-link&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://ridingbytes.com/downloads/Master%20Thesis%20-%20Impact%20of%20Netiquette%20on%20Email%20Communication.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
        MBA Master Thesis - Impact of Netiquette on Email Communication
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;rb-download&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://ridingbytes.com/downloads/Email%20Netiquette%20Guide%201.3-en.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
        Netiquette Guide (English language)
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;rb-download&#34;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://ridingbytes.com/downloads/Email%20Netiquette%20Guide%201.2-de.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;
        Netiquette Guide (German language)
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;container rb-divider&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;dividewhite2&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;e-block-centered&#34;&gt;
      &amp;mdash; &lt;img src=&#34;http://ridingbytes.com/img/rb_logo_32x32.png&#34; /&gt; &amp;mdash;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;dividewhite2&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>